{
  "topic": "6.4",
  "title": "Скобка в степени",
  "types": [
    {
      "id": "6.4.1",
      "title": "",
      "prototypes": [
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.1",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x+3} = 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 24 },
          "unic": true
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.2",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x - 2} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 127 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.3",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x + 10} = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.4",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x - 7} = -3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -20 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.5",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x + 20} = 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 7 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.6",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x - 11} = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 75 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.7",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x + 5} = -4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -69 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.8",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x + 1} = 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 0 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.9",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x - 28} = 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 55 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.10",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x + 8} = -1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -9 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.11",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x + 7} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 118 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.12",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x + 30} = -3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -57 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.13",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x} = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 64 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.14",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x + 12} = -2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -20 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.15",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x - 5} = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 13 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.16",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x - 16} = -3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -11 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.17",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x + 9} = 3 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 18 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.18",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x - 10} = -2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.19",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x + 4} = 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.1.20",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt[3]{x - 18} = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 82 }
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "6.4.2",
      "title": "",
      "prototypes": [
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.1",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x - 5)^3 = 64 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 9 },
          "unic": true
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.2",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x + 2)^3 = 64 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.3",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x - 3)^3 = 125 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 8 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.4",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x + 7)^3 = -27 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -10 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.5",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x - 1)^3 = 8 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.6",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x + 4)^3 = -64 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -8 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.7",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x + 10)^3 = 27 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -7 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.8",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x - 6)^3 = -8 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 4 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.9",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large x^3 = 125 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.10",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x + 3)^3 = 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.11",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x - 8)^3 = 64 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 12 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.12",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x + 5)^3 = -27 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -8 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.13",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x - 2)^3 = 64 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 6 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.14",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x + 9)^3 = 8 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -7 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.15",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x - 4)^3 = -64 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 0 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.16",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x + 6)^3 = 27 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.17",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x - 7)^3 = 1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 8 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.18",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x + 1)^3 = -8 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.19",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x - 5)^3 = 125 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 10 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.4.2.20",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large (x + 8)^3 = -1 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": -9 }
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
